{
  "title": "Idioms with the phrasal verb run",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "The Australian Labour Party doesn't currently have any politicians that would be capable of successfully ....... the Prime Minister at the next federal election",
      "answers": [
        "running away with",
        "running for",
        "running against",
        "running down"
      ],
      "correct": "running against"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Hillary Clinton has not ruled out ........ president at the next election. ",
      "answers": [
        "running off",
        "running for",
        "running against",
        "running down"
      ],
      "correct": "running for"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "I decided to ........ my girlfriend and get married when I found out that her parents didn't like me because of my religion. ",
      "answers": ["run away with", "run for", "run against", "run through"],
      "correct": "run away with"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "My parents were very disappointed when they found out that I had ........ all their money. ",
      "answers": ["run off with", "run for", "run against", "run through"],
      "correct": "run off with"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "The ........ apartment block failed to attract any buyers and was taken off the market so renovations could be carried out. ",
      "answers": ["run off", "run through", "run after", "run down"],
      "correct": "run down"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Many children try to .........from home for one reason or another at least once during their childhood. ",
      "answers": ["run away", "run for", "run against", "run down"],
      "correct": "run away"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "It's so nice to ........ you again after all this time. I don't think I've seen you for at least twenty years. ",
      "answers": ["run out", "run into", "run after", "run off"],
      "correct": "run into"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Can you please ........ our marketing campaign with me one more time? I don't quite fully understand it yet",
      "answers": ["run off", "run into", "run through", "run after"],
      "correct": "run through"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Our dog loves to .........the mail truck.",
      "answers": ["run through", "run over", "run after", "run in"],
      "correct": "run after"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "My mum had a ........ with my teacher for not allowing me to go to the toilet during class.",
      "answers": ["run-on", "run-in", "rundown", "run-off"],
      "correct": "run-in"
    }
  ]
}
